National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty Records
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Video, 1985-2005; nam_apap298-8; 5.40 cubic ft.
  - Wrongly Convicted - How the Innocent are Sent to Death Row. A Definitive Symposium, Professor Michael Radelet, University of Florida, 1999 September 16; nam_apap298-8_194 (Vhs 189)
  - Unlabeled VHS tape, Undated; nam_apap298-8_195 (Vhs 190)